Hugh Mugo Mwaura

hughmugo8@gmail.com | 0797554827 | nakuru, nai

www.linkedin.com/in/teddy-brilliant-271406188/ | github.com/xtec254

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a front end developer and programmer.having experience in angular,html ,css and javascript.i have a background study in computer science which has helped in the understanding of computers and its both direct and indirect relations to it

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- configuration of a switch
- maintenance of a live server
- · creation of various websites

•

EDUCATION

st paul's university November 2023

computer science, system security

limuru

• Coursework: introduction to computer programming, object oriented programming, application developement for the internet, introduction to internet technologies

WORK EXPERIENCE

KenGen January 2023 – March 2023

ICTO OLKRIA

- · system maintenance and setup
- user support
- · network configuration
- website developement
- hardware manitenance and repairs
- computer assembly
- learnt about presentations

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

KenGen

January 2023 – March 2023

ICT

naivasha ,Okaria

- assembling computers
- troubleshooting of hardware and software
- installation of windows ,office ,SAP programs and emails configurations
- local area network design ,installation and troubleshooting
- computer repair and maintenance
- user support
- track IT systems
- · fiber optic cable splicing
- network maintenance & trouble shooting
- Building a website as side project

SKILLS

front end development: angular,javascript,css ,html

PROJECTS

<u>**qr** code generator</u> | html,css,javascript

• this is a qr code generaator for customised urls and any typed data

March 2023 - March 2023

REFERENCES

samson mwikya, supervisor smwikya@kengen.co.ke, 0724948449